Pavan Bharadwaj Undavalli

RPA Developer

Experienced software developer with 3+ years of a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology and services industry. Focused and adaptable professional skilled at flexing with different usability requirements and optimizing code. Looking for an opportunity where i can utilize my professional expertise and skills to grow my organization and my technical career growth.





undavallipavanbharadwaj@gmail.com



8919795820



hyderabad, india

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Techmahindra

04/2019 - Present

Hyderabad

Roles and Responsibilities

- Trained on Robotic Process Automation technology and Received UiPath RPA Developer Advanced Certification.
- Designed, developed and implemented UI Path code to automate various end to end processes.
- Hands on experience in using W e b automation, Data scraping, Excel automation, Excel Macros, OCR Engines, Screen scraping, Email automation, PDF automation, Selectors.
- Implemented selectors for interacting with window and web browsers for continuous navigation of applications.
- Experience in using RE-Framework and Exceptional handling. Used UiPath Orchestrator for deployment, scheduling, and monitoring UiPath bot activities.
- Worked with business teams to create Process definition document (PDD) and developed solution design document (SDD).
- Used UiPath automation activities such as type into, click, get text, select item, on image appear and element exists to create sequential workflows
- Good understanding of bot development and UiPath RPA lifecycle.
- Extensively worked on debugging workflows for fixing errors.
- Used TACTIX (AI) tool to resolve various tickets within the project. To support staff to focus on high value tasks and reduction in AHT. Reduced dependency on SME's, improved knowledge retention and staff productivity and new engineer onboarding time.

phone banking officer **ICICI Bank**

12/2017 - 01/2019

Hyderabad

Roles and Responsibilities

- Resolved customer queries through E-mail channel and with many other company tools and resources
- Handled escalation E-mails and calls of customer and provided best possible solutions
- Explained organization's procedures, products, and services in detail to boost sales and support superior customer experiences

EDUCATION

B.tech

Mallareddy institute of technology and science

05/2013 - 05/2017

Courses

ECE

SKILLS

UiPath

MS Office(Excel, PowerPoint, Word)

AUTOMATION PROJECTS

- 1. Governance Report
- 2. Ticket statistics and SLA dashboard Report
- 3. Covid-19 Report
- 4. App Monthly Analysis by service
- 5. Timesheet Entry Automation

CERTIFICATIONS

RPA Developer

Completed RPA developer foundation certification from UI Path Academy.

UiPath RPA developer Advanced Certification

Achieved UiPath RPA developer Advanced Certification from UI Path

UIPath RPA Developer

Completed UI Path RPA Developer course from Udemy website.

Agile Process Management

Received Agile Process Management course completion certificate

AI (101)

Received certificate of achievement from Tech Mahindra

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Playing Cricket

Playing Chess

Playing Table Tennis

Playing Badminton